{
  "Armory": [
    {
      "id": 1,
      "question": "Contaminated items generated by incidents involving blood-borne pathogens are disposed where?",
      "answer": "Biohazard containers are located in the weapons cleaning areas of CCSFS and PSFB",
      "ref": "EXPLAIN/PERFORM BLOODBOURNE PATHOGEN EXPOSURE CONTROL PRECEDURES - 45 SFS BBP Exposure Control Plan",
      "correct": 0,
      "wrong": 0,
      "asked": 0
    },
    {
      "id": 2,
      "question": "Whom may authorize changes to AF Form 1473?",
      "answer": "NCOIC/Armory Chief",
      "ref": "EXPLAIN/PERFORM CHANGEOVER PROCEDURES (CRITICAL) 45 SFS OI 31-1 V4 Chap 2 Para 2.2.5-2.2.5.3",
      "correct": 0,
      "wrong": 0,
      "asked": 0
    },
    {
      "id": 3,
      "question": "All 'issue' or 'maintenance' items accounted for on the AF Form 1473 must have what in place of the item to account for them?",
      "answer": "AF Form 1297, Temporary Issue Receipt or DD Form 2825, Internal Receipt,",
      "ref": "EXPLAIN/PERFORM CHANGEOVER PROCEDURES (CRITICAL) 45 SFS OI 31-1 V4 Chap 2 Para 2.2.5-2.2.5.3",
      "correct": 0,
      "wrong": 0,
      "asked": 0
    },
    {
      "id": 4,
      "question": "True or False: You may conduct issue/turn-in of weapons during inventory.",
      "answer": "False",
      "ref": "EXPLAIN/PERFORM CHANGEOVER PROCEDURES (CRITICAL) 45 SFS OI 31-1 V4 Chap 2 Para 2.2.5-2.2.5.3",
      "correct": 0,
      "wrong": 0,
      "asked": 0
    },
    {
      "id": 5,
      "question": "Do not allow more than ______ visitors if you are the only armed attendant IAW AF Form 2047, Explosives Facility License.",
      "answer": "2",
      "ref": "EXPLAIN/PERFORM ENTRY CONTROL PROCEDURES (CRITICAL) 45 SFS OI 31-1 V4 Chap 2 Para 2.3- 2.3.4",
      "correct": 0,
      "wrong": 0,
      "asked": 0
    },
    {
      "id": 6,
      "question": "Tours or visitations are to be cleared through whom?",
      "answer": "NCOIC/Armory Chief.",
      "ref": "EXPLAIN/PERFORM ENTRY CONTROL PROCEDURES (CRITICAL) 45 SFS OI 31-1 V4 Chap 2 Para 2.3- 2.3.4",
      "correct": 0,
      "wrong": 0,
      "asked": 0
    },
    {
      "id": 7,
      "question": "Ensure personnel requesting entry have a _________ to enter and a valid photo ID.",
      "answer": "valid reason",
      "ref": "EXPLAIN/PERFORM ENTRY CONTROL PROCEDURES (CRITICAL) 45 SFS OI 31-1 V4 Chap 2 Para 2.3- 2.3.4",
      "correct": 0,
      "wrong": 0,
      "asked": 0
    },
    {
      "id": 8,
      "question": "During normal operations, the number of personnel allowed access to the armory will be limited to ________ personnel IAW AF Form 2047.",
      "answer": "eight (8)",
      "ref": "EXPLAIN/PERFORM ENTRY CONTROL PROCEDURES (CRITICAL) 45 SFS OI 31-1 V4 Chap 2 Para 2.3- 2.3.4",
      "correct": 0,
      "wrong": 0,
      "asked": 0
    },
    {
      "id": 9,
      "question": "Visitors will be given _______ upon entry to armory.",
      "answer": "A safety briefing",
      "ref": "EXPLAIN/PERFORM ENTRY CONTROL PROCEDURES (CRITICAL) 45 SFS OI 31-1 V4 Chap 2 Para 2.3- 2.3.4",
      "correct": 0,
      "wrong": 0,
      "asked": 0
    },
    {
      "id": 10,
      "question": "On-duty armorers are required to be armed at all times. The primary weapon is the _____ with ____ of ammunition.",
      "answer": "M18 Pistol/30 rds ammo",
      "ref": "EXPLAIN/PERFORM ARMORY PROTECTION CONSIDERATIONS 45 SFS OI 31-1 V4 Chap 2 Para 2.4-2.4.10",
      "correct": 0,
      "wrong": 0,
      "asked": 0
    },
    {
      "id": 11,
      "question": "When not in use for issue/turn-in, how must racks be configured?",
      "answer": "closed and locked",
      "ref": "EXPLAIN/PERFORM ARMORY PROTECTION CONSIDERATIONS 45 SFS OI 31-1 V4 Chap 2 Para 2.4-2.4.10",
      "correct": 0,
      "wrong": 0,
      "asked": 0
    },
    {
      "id": 12,
      "question": "How often are alarm authentication codes changed?",
      "answer": "every six months, unless compromised",
      "ref": "EXPLAIN/PERFORM ARMORY PROTECTION CONSIDERATIONS 45 SFS OI 31-1 V4 Chap 2 Para 2.4-2.4.10",
      "correct": 0,
      "wrong": 0,
      "asked": 0
    },
    {
      "id": 13,
      "question": "Where should damaged munitions be stored?",
      "answer": "Store damaged munitions by type in a munitions can marked appropriately with the national stock number and lot number.",
      "ref": "EXPLAIN/PERFORM WEAPONS AND EXPLOSIVES SAFETY PROCEDURES (CRITICAL) 45 SFS OI 31-1 V4 Chap 2 Para 2.22",
      "correct": 0,
      "wrong": 0,
      "asked": 0
    },
    {
      "id": 14,
      "question": "In the event of a robbery/attempt, what form must you complete once the scene is secured?",
      "answer": "AF Form 439, Robbery Checklist.",
      "ref": "EXPLAIN/PERFORM DURESS ALARM/ANTI-ROBBERY PROCEDURES (CRITICAL) 45 SFS OI 31-1 V4 Chap 2 Para 2.5-2.5.6",
      "correct": 0,
      "wrong": 0,
      "asked": 0
    },
    {
      "id": 15,
      "question": "How often are duress alarms tested?",
      "answer": "Weekly",
      "ref": "EXPLAIN/PERFORM DURESS ALARM TESTS 45 SFS OI 31-1 V4 Chap 2 Para 2.2.12",
      "correct": 0,
      "wrong": 0,
      "asked": 0
    },
    {
      "id": 16,
      "question": "What form is used to document alarm tests?",
      "answer": "AF Form 340, Sensor Alarm Data.",
      "ref": "EXPLAIN/PERFORM DURESS ALARM TESTS 45 SFS OI 31-1 V4 Chap 2 Para 2.2.12",
      "correct": 0,
      "wrong": 0,
      "asked": 0
    },
    {
      "id": 17,
      "question": "How should the M240B be issued to the arming individual?",
      "answer": "'butt' first, muzzle elevated, bolt to the rear (open) position and safety in the safe position.",
      "ref": "EXPLAIN/PERFORM WEAPONS ISSUE AND TURN-IN PROCEDURES FOR M240B MACHINEGUN AFMAN 31-129 Chap 24 Para 24.1-24.7.4",
      "correct": 0,
      "wrong": 0,
      "asked": 0
    },
    {
      "id": 18,
      "question": "Upon receiving the M240B for turn in, the armorer will:",
      "answer": "Ensure the safety is in the safe position and open the cover. Visually inspect the cover, feed tray, chamber, and receiver to ensure the MG contains no ammunition and is safe for storage. Close the cover and place the safety in the fire (F) position. With the right-hand, pull and hold the cocking handle to the rear, with the lefthand, pull the trigger. Allow the bolt to slowly move to the forward (closed) position by riding the cocking handle forward. Do not allow the bolt to slam forward.",
      "ref": "EXPLAIN/PERFORM WEAPONS ISSUE AND TURN-IN PROCEDURES FOR M240B MACHINEGUN AFMAN 31-129 Chap 24 Para 24.1-24.7.4",
      "correct": 0,
      "wrong": 0,
      "asked": 0
    },
    {
      "id": 19,
      "question": "Upon receipt of the shotgun for turn in, what must the armorer accomplish?",
      "answer": "Visually inspect the chamber, receiver and magazine to ensure the shotgun contains no ammunition and is safe for storage. Push the fore-end to the forward (action closed) position, place the weapon on fire (red band or red dot showing) and dry-fire into the clearing barrel. After dry-firing, the safety is returned to the safe position.",
      "ref": "EXPLAIN/PERFORM WEAPONS ISSUE AND TURN-IN PROCEDURES FOR M870 SHOTGUN AFMAN 31-129 Chap 20 Para 20.1-20.5.6",
      "correct": 0,
      "wrong": 0,
      "asked": 0
    },
    {
      "id": 20,
      "question": "After removal from the rack and prior to issue, what must the armorer accomplish regarding the M870 shotgun?",
      "answer": "Place the muzzle into the clearing barrel aiming point in line with the axis of the barrel and ensure the safety is in the safe position (red band or dot not showing). Do not place fingers into the trigger guard. While depressing the action bar lock, grasp the fore-end with the “non-shooting” hand and pull it to the rear, opening the action. Visually inspect the chamber, receiver, and magazine to ensure no ammunition is present. Issue the shotgun to the individual, “butt” first, muzzle elevated, action open and safety in the safe position.",
      "ref": "EXPLAIN/PERFORM WEAPONS ISSUE AND TURN-IN PROCEDURES FOR M870 SHOTGUN AFMAN 31-129 Chap 20 Para 20.1-20.5.6",
      "correct": 0,
      "wrong": 0,
      "asked": 0
    },
    {
      "id": 21,
      "question": "After removal from and prior to issue to arming individual, what steps must the armorer accomplish concerning the M249 Light Machine Gun?",
      "answer": "Place the muzzle into the clearing barrel aiming point in line with the axis of the barrel. Pull and hold the cocking handle to the rear, locking the bolt to the rear (open) position. Return the cocking handle to the forward position and place the safety to the safe (red band not visible) position. Do not place fingers inside the trigger guard. Open the cover and visually inspect the cover, feed tray, chamber, magazine well (insert two fingers) and receiver to ensure no ammunition is present. Issue the AR to the individual, “butt” first, muzzle elevated, bolt in the rear (open) position, and safety in the safe position. Ensure the individual raises the feed tray, inspects the chamber, and then closes the cover prior to acceptance.",
      "ref": "EXPLAIN/PERFORM WEAPONS ISSUE AND TURN-IN PROCEDURES FOR M249 LIGHT MACHINEGUN AFMAN 31-129 Chap 23 Para 23.1-23.7",
      "correct": 0,
      "wrong": 0,
      "asked": 0
    },
    {
      "id": 22,
      "question": "After receiving the M249 Light Machine Gun from the arming individual for turn in, explain what steps must be accomplished prior to securing the weapon in the rack.",
      "answer": "Ensure the safety is in the safe position and open the cover. Visually inspect the cover, feed tray, chamber, receiver, and magazine well (insert two fingers) to ensure the AR contains no ammunition and is safe for storage. Close the cover and place the safety in the fire position. With the right-hand, grasp the “cocking handle” and pull rearward. With the left-hand, pull the trigger. Allow the bolt to slowly move to the forward (closed) position by “riding” the cocking handle forward. Do not allow the bolt to slam forward.",
      "ref": "EXPLAIN/PERFORM WEAPONS ISSUE AND TURN-IN PROCEDURES FOR M249 LIGHT MACHINEGUN AFMAN 31-129 Chap 23 Para 23.1-23.7",
      "correct": 0,
      "wrong": 0,
      "asked": 0
    },
    {
      "id": 23,
      "question": "If munitions or weapons are stolen, immediately notify _____, the ______ and initiate anti-robbery tasks.",
      "answer": "BDOC, NCOIC/Armory Chief",
      "ref": "EXPLAIN/PERFORM WEAPONS ISSUE AND TURN-IN PROCEDURES FOR M249 LIGHT MACHINEGUN AFMAN 31-129 Chap 23 Para 23.1-23.7",
      "correct": 0,
      "wrong": 0,
      "asked": 0
    },
    {
      "id": 24,
      "question": "How would you issue a radio to staff personnel?",
      "answer": "utilizing an AF Form 1297.",
      "ref": "EXPLAIN/PERFORM COMMUNICATIONS EQUIPMENT PROCEDURES 45 SFS OI 31-1 V4 Chap 2 Para 2.21-2.21.2",
      "correct": 0,
      "wrong": 0,
      "asked": 0
    },
    {
      "id": 25,
      "question": "What is accomplished during ammo blocking?",
      "answer": "Munitions blocking enables the armory to verify accountability of munitions, as well as its serviceability, while also “relaxing” the spring mechanisms in the magazines.",
      "ref": "EXPLAIN/PERFORM MUNITIONS BLOCKING 45 SFS OI 31-1 V4 Chap 2 Para 2.19-2.19.4",
      "correct": 0,
      "wrong": 0,
      "asked": 0
    },
    {
      "id": 26,
      "question": "Flight Sergeant/Chiefs should identify _____ percent of their flight per cycle to conduct blocking",
      "answer": "10",
      "ref": "EXPLAIN/PERFORM MUNITIONS BLOCKING 45 SFS OI 31-1 V4 Chap 2 Para 2.19-2.19.4",
      "correct": 0,
      "wrong": 0,
      "asked": 0
    },
    {
      "id": 27,
      "question": "The armorer can deny access to weapon(s) and contact the Flight Sergeant/Chief for any individual...",
      "answer": "who is currently identified on the DNA memorandum, not on a current duty roster, appears to have been drinking alcoholic beverages 8-hrs prior to duty, is acting in an irresponsible/inappropriate manner as to cause concern, or any person believed to be emotionally or physically incapable of bearing arms.",
      "ref": "EXPLAIN/PERFORM WEAPONS DENIAL (CRITICAL) 45 SFS OI 31-1 V4 Chap 2 Para 2.17-2.17.2.2",
      "correct": 0,
      "wrong": 0,
      "asked": 0
    },
    {
      "id": 28,
      "question": "Upon verbal notification of withdrawal of authority to bear firearms, armorers wil IMMEDIATELY...",
      "answer": "Stop all actions and tag the affected individual's assigned weapons with an orange DO NOT ARM card to prevent any accidental issuance to unauthorized personnel.",
      "ref": "EXPLAIN/PERFORM WEAPONS DENIAL (CRITICAL) 45 SFS OI 31-1 V4 Chap 2 Para 2.17-2.17.2.2",
      "correct": 0,
      "wrong": 0,
      "asked": 0
    },
    {
      "id": 29,
      "question": "Weapons are only issued to those individuals who are properly equipped. Explain.",
      "answer": "Wearing web gear, munitions pouches, holsters",
      "ref": "EXPLAIN/PERFORM WEAPONS DENIAL (CRITICAL) 45 SFS OI 31-1 V4 Chap 2 Para 2.17-2.17.2.2",
      "correct": 0,
      "wrong": 0,
      "asked": 0
    },
    {
      "id": 30,
      "question": "Explain your actions/reactions to a small fire in the armory.",
      "answer": "If the fire is small and poses no immediate threat to personnel or equipment, attempt to contain the fire using a fire extinguisher.",
      "ref": "EXPLAIN/PERFORM ARMORY FIRE PROCEDURES 45 SFS OI 31-1 V4 Chap 2 Para 2.7-2.7.5",
      "correct": 0,
      "wrong": 0,
      "asked": 0
    },
    {
      "id": 31,
      "question": "Explain your actions/reactions to a LARGE fire in the armory.",
      "answer": "If the fire is too large, evacuate the armory immediately, notify BDOC and note the time and if any explosives were engulfed in flames, if possible.",
      "ref": "EXPLAIN/PERFORM ARMORY FIRE PROCEDURES 45 SFS OI 31-1 V4 Chap 2 Para 2.7-2.7.5",
      "correct": 0,
      "wrong": 0,
      "asked": 0
    },
    {
      "id": 32,
      "question": "How often are weapons cleaned and lubed?",
      "answer": "Once per work cycle",
      "ref": "EXPLAIN/PERFORM WEAPONS CLEANING AND INSPECTION PROCEDURES 45 SFS OI 31-1 V4 Chap 2 Para 2.18-2.18.9",
      "correct": 0,
      "wrong": 0,
      "asked": 0
    },
    {
      "id": 33,
      "question": "After initial cleaning, post firing, when should a second cleaning occur?",
      "answer": "Within one week of firing or on next duty shift.",
      "ref": "EXPLAIN/PERFORM WEAPONS CLEANING AND INSPECTION PROCEDURES 45 SFS OI 31-1 V4 Chap 2 Para 2.18-2.18.9",
      "correct": 0,
      "wrong": 0,
      "asked": 0
    },
    {
      "id": 34,
      "question": "What are the required cleaning standards that should be complied with at all times:",
      "answer": "Weapons free of all carbon in accessible areas. Weapons free of rust, dust, dirt, and excessive oil. Barrels cleaned with a bore brush and patches. Weapon sights free of dust and lightly oiled.",
      "ref": "EXPLAIN/PERFORM WEAPONS CLEANING AND INSPECTION PROCEDURES 45 SFS OI 31-1 V4 Chap 2 Para 2.18-2.18.9",
      "correct": 0,
      "wrong": 0,
      "asked": 0
    },
    {
      "id": 35,
      "question": "After conducting and inspection of a weapon, post cleaning, what muct the armorer perform?",
      "answer": "The inspecting armorer will function-check the weapon to ensure proper assembly.",
      "ref": "EXPLAIN/PERFORM WEAPONS CLEANING AND INSPECTION PROCEDURES 45 SFS OI 31-1 V4 Chap 2 Para 2.18-2.18.9",
      "correct": 0,
      "wrong": 0,
      "asked": 0
    },
    {
      "id": 36,
      "question": "For temporary storage of a POF, what must the accomplish in the presence of the weapon owner?",
      "answer": "Armorers conduct a complete inspection of firearm(s) to be stored in the presence of the owner and annotate any damage on pre-generated condition sheets.",
      "ref": "EXPLAIN/PERFORM PSFB STORAGE OF PRIVATELY OWNED FIREARMS (POF) AND MUNITIONS 45 SFS OI 31-1 V4 Chap 2 Para 2.29-2.29.6.4",
      "correct": 0,
      "wrong": 0,
      "asked": 0
    },
    {
      "id": 37,
      "question": "POFs stored on a temporary basis require approval from the ________ prior to releasing back to owner.",
      "answer": "Air Force Security Forces Center (AFSFC)",
      "ref": "EXPLAIN/PERFORM PSFB STORAGE OF PRIVATELY OWNED FIREARMS (POF) AND MUNITIONS 45 SFS OI 31-1 V4 Chap 2 Para 2.29-2.29.6.4",
      "correct": 0,
      "wrong": 0,
      "asked": 0
    },
    {
      "id": 38,
      "question": "Long term storage of POF's is authorized for whom?",
      "answer": "Any person residing in unaccompanied housing, FAMCAMP, the marina, staying in a temporary lodging facility or as per DFC.",
      "ref": "EXPLAIN/PERFORM PSFB STORAGE OF PRIVATELY OWNED FIREARMS (POF) AND MUNITIONS 45 SFS OI 31-1 V4 Chap 2 Para 2.29-2.29.6.4",
      "correct": 0,
      "wrong": 0,
      "asked": 0
    }
  ]
}